<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Blackjack</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <string name="key_num_decks">numDecks</string>
    <string name="blackjack_rules">Blackjack Rules</string>
    <string name="blackjack_rules_description">"How to Play:\nTwo cards each are dealt to the dealer and the player. The player’s cards are dealt face up. Only the dealer’s first card is dealt face up. A card numbered 2 through 10 is worth its face value. Jacks, queens and kings each count as 10. Aces can count as 1 or 11 – whichever value is more beneficial to the player. If the sum of the player’s two initial cards is 21 (that is, the player was dealt a card valued at 10 and an ace, which counts as 11 in this situation), the player has “blackjack” and the dealer’s face-down card is revealed. If the dealer does not have blackjack, the player immediately wins the game; otherwise, the hand is a “push” (a tie) and no one wins the hand. If the player does not have blackjack, the player can begin taking additional cards one at a time. These cards are dealt face up, and the player decides when to stop taking cards. If the player “busts” (that is, the sum of the player’s cards exceeds 21), the game is over, and the player loses. When the player stands (stops taking cards), the dealer’s hidden card is revealed. If the dealer’s total is 16 or less, the dealer must take another card; otherwise, the dealer must stay. The dealer must continue to take cards until the sum of the dealer’s cards is greater than or equal to 17. If the dealer exceeds 21, the player wins. Otherwise, the hand with the higher point total wins. If the dealer and the player have the same point total, the game is a “push,” and no one wins.\n\nBetting:\nBefore dealing, the user can place a bet less than or equal to the user's available cash. Betting during play is disabled (unless the user doubles down). When the player loses all their money, the user can restart with $1000 cash.\n\nOther rules:\nPlayers may opt to allow surrender-ing and doubling down. When the player surrenders, they lose half their initial bet and lose the round, allowing the player to reduce losses on a play. When the player doubles down, the user automatically draws one card and stands for the round. This move doubles the initial bet, but can only be player if the player has enough cash to make the play."</string>

</resources>